I look up to the stars and reach for
the sky I believe in tomorrow if we try!
Hey!
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
We share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one dream.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the good times.
We share the good times.
Let's go, baby, baby, oh,
we share the one world.
It's hard to see for you and me.
Through the darkness
that is in this world.
So hard to see, but to believe.
In where we need to go.
Yes, you and me, it's true that we.
Feel the rush brought on by this world.
Through head to feet, I feel the beat.
Getting me to walk on, oh yeah.
Share the music, no matter what.
Share the one dream, believe in yourself.
Share the good times, take my hand now.
Share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try high.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah.
Come on let's go everybody.
Oh we share the music.
Come on let's go baby baby.
Oh we share the one world.
Oh as we chase we're being chased.
From the top we go on straight and wild.
We're on our way, I've got to say.
Hey, I want to share your style.
Now here it starts, so don't lose heart.
They're bound to lose to this flavor.
From boot to hood, I feel so good.
I will be free to be, oh yeah.
Share the music, even if I.
Share the one dream, I know where you are.
Share the good times,
share the one world now.
I look up to the stars.
And reach for the sky.
No matter what.
I'll try no matter how high.
So let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in tomorrow.
If we try.
I know that you are there.
Just on the other side.
Wait there for me.
Soon it will be you and I.
Then let us go.
Beyond, far and wide.
I believe in the one world.
If we try.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Come on, let's go, everybody.
Oh, we share the music.
Come on, let's go, baby, baby.
Oh, we share the one world.
I'd heard rumors you were
somewhere on the archipelago,
but I chalked them up as ghost stories.
Yet here you are, sticking your
neck out for these rookies.
You just can't shake those
instincts, can you, Rayleigh?
Once a pirate, always a pirate.
I'd be more than happy to retire in
peace and live out the quiet life.
But it's a little tough to do when the
Navy keeps hanging wanted posters of me.
You were a member of the
Roger Pirates, Rayleigh.
Do you really think your
crimes can be forgotten?
But if we were to make an
honest attempt at capturing you,
that would require some serious
preparation on our part.
Wow, I'm so relieved.
That old man has really got some power.
All of our attacks went through
him as if he were a ghost.
But when Rayleigh attacked, it hit.
Why don't you just look the
other way and let these kids go?
What's the harm?
Come on.
What reality are you living in?
You know,
there's no way I can just
let them off the hook
Not when we have to answer
to the Celestial Dragons.
Maybe HQ's got to keep
them happy and that won't
do it I'd appreciate it
if you don't interfere.
Let's go!
Everyone, start running
and look after yourselves!
We can't win this one!
We're too weak!
Get moving!
He knows when he's beat.
Well, ain't that a pain?
Franky, come on!
Not before I let loose one final attack.
With all of my cola energy.
Go to fire!
How'd that feel, you mechanical ass?
Now hurry, run!
Hey, old man, thanks a lot!
Sure thing.
Best of luck to you.
Sacred Yata Mirrors.
I can't see!
I don't think he's trying to help us see.
You're staying put.
Feels good to hold a blade again.
Amano Murakumo, soy!
This is disappointing.
I was expecting a laid-back,
hassle-free island excursion.
Life is nothing but a
series of surprises, Kizaru.
That light from before! It's gone!
I guess the old man saved us again!
I was so scared!
It appears he's the Dark King, after all.
I've never seen anyone put
Uncle through a fight like that.
We were so close to closing the
book on Roro Noah's days of crime.
PX1!
Finish Roro Noah off first!
He's barely alive!
Crap, this is bad.
Hey, Franky, do me a favor
and keep Nami safe, okay?
Just keep on running. We'll be fine.
You take care of yourself, okay?
What are you doing, Sanji?
I've got to help Moose up and Zoro.
Put me down.
Just leave me.
Save yourself.
Don't be a moron.
Right now, you're even more
weak and useless than I am.
We're getting out of here together.
Those were Luffy's orders,
and I'm sticking to them.
Huh?
Wait, do I hear...
Come on, hurry up!
You go on without me.
It's fine, I'll hold him back.
No, don't do it, Brooke!
You don't know how strong he is!
He'll rip you apart!
Never fear!
Run on, my friend!
This is what must be done!
There comes a time when a man
must put everything on the line!
No bones about it.
That was pretty pointless.
Brooke, no!
Go away!
Leave me alone!
Get the hell away from
them, you stupid cyborg!
Sanji!
Ow, my leg!
Move, Sanji!
He's gonna shoot you!
Moron, why aren't you running?
Huh?
Even if you distract me, my subordinates
are quite capable on their own.
I dropped you!
I'm sorry, Zoro!
It was an accident!
Looks like they're in trouble over there!
You've got plenty of trouble yourself!
But just to be fair, I won't use
my battle-axe on you this time!
That's a push-up!
Luffy! Why?
How can his attacks work on him
when Luffy's made of proper?
What the hell?
Chopper, we have to keep moving! Sachi!
Sachi!
Everybody's gonna die!
No, Gecko, it's too dangerous!
Get the hell away from my friends!
Now, rumble ball!
It's Chopper!
I like Little Chopper better!
What exactly am I looking at?
It's even worse than
what the others told me.
That's an interesting
power you've got there.
It's too bad you don't seem
to have any control over it.
This is what it's come to Even
if he beats him, then what?
I don't know what's going on But he
seems confused. Now's our chance.
Sanji. Brooke. Get up. Snap out of it.
Chopper bought us some time.
We gotta move.
We wanna live, right?
Hey, you're blowing our
chance. Brooke. Sanji.
Stand down, PX1.
This is officially too much.
I can't take it!
Just how many of these guys are there?
It isn't fair!
It's him.
It's the real Kuma.
I see you survived.
You are more Noah.
Just barely.
I've got your mercy to thank for that.
What are you doing, Zoro?
This is no time to talk
to the enemy. Let's go.
If you could take a vacation,
where is it you'd like to go?
Hey, Zoro!
Come on, let's get out
of here while we can.
S-S-Solo!
He's gone!
What the hell did you do to him?
You!
Where is he?
You bring him back here, you monster!
Zoro!
What did you do?
No!
Zoro
Chopper, stop this!
You've lost control?
Zoro, where the hell are you?
This beast has gone mad, but
that's not what worries me.
I want to know what he's doing here.
Well, Bartholomew Kuma,
can't trust pirates.
The Seven Warlords are
supposed to be at Navy HQ.
too.
I wish I could help, but
there's nothing I can do.
It's like Saru was erased.
I'm gonna guess that means
this guy's the real Kuma.
There's no question.
That power he used, I've seen it before.
Back on Thriller Bark, he
erased a girl like that.
Just made her disappear, and
that was the last I saw of her.
Let's just hope he's still alive
Hey, what the hell did
that guy do to Zoro?
Where is he?
You think I'm gonna answer you?
Did you forget I'm the
world's most guarded man?
But someone might tell
you he can send you flying
for three days and nights
with those paw pads.
Can't say if it's true or
not, but that's the rumor.
Only Kuma knows where they go.
But there's no way you're going to
find your friend on these islands?
Or anywhere else around
here, for that matter.
He'll probably land on the
other side of the world.
What?
Say something, dammit!
Tell us what you did!
Tell us where you sent Zoro!
So that's the real deal, huh?
The first three were bad enough.
And now he shows up to finish the job.
There's no way to win!
What kind of power is that?
Stop it! Get back!
I've got 8,000 men under my command!
Don't make me unleash them on you!
Usopp, he's behind you!
Get down!
Oh crap!
Don't interfere.
He erased him? But why?
That was Pucci he just hit.
What's your problem, you fool?
That was your ally.
Just run!
Move, you guys!
Move me, huh? Just go! Get out of there!
We can figure out a plan once we're safe!
Run!
All right, you heard him.
But Zoro...
The captain just said we can
figure it out after we're safe!
Come on!
Come on, buddy.
That last beam just grazed me.
I can help you walk.
Go, you two.
I'll cover you.
Stop it, Brooke!
That's crazy!
I'll protect you.
Even if it costs me my life!
Oh, but I'm already dead, I suppose.
Brooke, no!
Damn it!
How the hell can I let this happen?
The bastards are racing all my
friends right in front of me!
Get back!
Sanji!
Start running, Usopp!
Not a chance!
I'm not going without you, Sanji!
Son of a bitch!
Sanji! Just run! Come on!
Nobody does that to my Gourmet!
Sachi!
No!
Get back!
Stay away!
Stop where you are! Get back! Blamestar!
One more! Blamestar!
Go away, please!
Just leave me alone!
Moose up, run!
Stop it!
Usopp
Soji
Damn you!
You can't win.
Don't fight.
He got Sanji!
What now?
What do we do?
It can't be!
They're all gone.
It's starting to sound like they
could really use my help over there.
There's only so much an old man can do.
I guess I'm not quite the
fighter I used to be So fending
off a Navy Admiral isn't
enough to make you satisfied,
huh?
Why don't you keep those
thoughts to yourself?
You're already making
me look bad, you know
Dark King Rayleigh correct
Kuma?
Wait, Luffy.
You can't be serious.
You're asking me to trust you?
That's entirely your decision.
But I'm putting my own
neck on the line, too.
All right.
I feel like I deserve an
explanation here. Kuma?
This matter is of no
consequence to the government,
so I have no obligation to
cooperate with the Navy.
And you deserve nothing of the sort.
You bastard!
Now, second gear!
Get the hell out of our way!
I'm right!
What the...
Luffy, no!
Come on, Jack, can't go!
Luffy!
Someone help me!
Nami!
Luffy!
Chopper, no!
Don't do it!
Damn it.
No more.
Please stop.
Stop it!
I can't leave her alone!
Luffy!
Robin!
The End
I don't know.
I couldn't save any of them.
What's wrong with me?
So, you're just gonna blast
him off like the rest?
You can't pull this mess without
an explanation, you know.
And boy, it had better be a good one.
You and I will never meet again.
Farewell, Striad.
Grove 12, the Sabaody Archipelago,
deep in the Grand Line.
On this day, the Straw Hat
Pirates, led by Captain Monkey D.
Luffy, came face to
face with true despair.
And one by one, they were eliminated.